copub.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy

This privacy policy applies to your use of the Copub website located at www.copub.com (the "Copub Site"), but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to them, or any relationships you may have with the businesses listed on the Copub Site.

The terms "we", "us", and "Copub" refer to B2B ULUSLARARASI YAYINCILIK MEDYA İNTERNET TİC. ve SAN. A.Ş. The terms "you" and "your" refer to you, as a user of any of the Copub Sites. The term "personal information" means information that you provide to us which personally identifies you to be contacted or identified, such as your name, phone number, email address, and any other data that is tied to such information. BY USING THE COPUB SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY AND SECURITY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE COPUB SITES. 

I. Information We Collect and How We Use It

Copub values your privacy. We limit the collection of personal information to those items necessary to fulfill the purposes identified below. If we use your information in a manner different than the purpose for which it is collected, then we will ask you for your consent prior to such use.

Account information. If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered on the Copub Sites, we ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address. We use your email address to send you updates and news, and contact you on behalf of other users (such as notification alerts from project or network activity).

Public Submissions. We store and may publicly display your public submissions on the site. When we display your submission, we do so together with your account name or chosen user name. The term "public submission" refers to the information that you submit or post to the Copub Sites for public display, such as information that you display as part of your public profile, recommendations, and/or publicly facing network pages. For purposes of clarification, information within a project workspace is private and not public, and will not be subject to this paragraph.

Feedback. If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any personal information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your communication.

Activity. We record information relating to your use of the Copub Site, such as the searches you undertake, the pages you view, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, time stamp information, transactions entered into, and parties transacted with on the Site. We use this type of information to administer the Copub Site and provide the highest possible level of service to you. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Copub Site. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information. 

Cookies. We might send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions.

Enforcement. We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Copub Site (including your personal information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our Terms of Service and Privacy Policy. 

Payment Informations: Please note that we do NOT store credit/debit card numbers, nor do we share customer details with any 3rd parties. If you choose to pay using a Credit Card, your credit card details are not stored by us and cannot be used by our staff.

II. Transfer of Information

Copub also reserve the right to disclose any information as reasonably believe is necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, enforce the Terms, including investigation of potential violations, detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, respond to user support requests, or protect the rights, property or safety of Copub, users and the public. 

III. Others' Information

You may choose to provide us with another person's e-mail address so that person may be invited to create an account on this website. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person about the invitation. By providing us with another person's e-mail address, you represent to us that you have obtained the consent of the person concerned as regards such disclosure to us of their personal information. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above. 

IV. Links

The Copub Site may contain links to third party sites to provide additional, value added services. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with those third parties, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites. 

V. Controlling Your Personal Data

To the extent you include personal information in your Public Submissions, such as a photo of yourself, third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your user account, and contact you. Please do not include information in your public submissions that you expect to keep private. 

Please also note that the private messages you send or receive using the Copub Sites', and/or the private information contained generally within your project workspaces, are only private to the extent that you, the sender/recipient, and/or all project participants with access to the information keep such information private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your private messages or a project participant publicly posts such information. 

VI. Security

Your account, is password protected. We use industry leading measures, including site wide secure sockets layer protocols to protect the private information, the project workspace information, and personal information that is stored in our database or sent using the Copub Sites. We limit the access to your personal information to those employees and contractors who need access to perform their job function, such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security on the Copub Sites, please contact us. Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that your personal information will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy. You hereby acknowledge that Copub is not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner. 

VII. E-mails and Opt-out

You may opt-out of receiving e-mails from Copub. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy. 

VIII. Terms and Modifications to this Privacy Policy

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page. If we make any material changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by sending an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any such changes will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our website. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of the Copub Site. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your personal information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of the Copub Site following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

IX. Dispute Resolution

If you believe that Copub has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may write to the Copub Privacy Office at support@copub.com. In your email, please describe in as much detail as possible ways in which you believe the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. 

X. Contacting the Website

Upon written request, subject to certain exceptions, Copub will inform you of the existence of your personal information and will give you access to that information. Access requests should be sent to our Privacy Officer, at support@copub.com. When requesting access to your personal information, we may request specific information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access, as well as to search for and provide the personal information that we hold about you.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of this website, or if you want to exercise any of the rights that you are given under this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at support@copub.com.
